This is Dae. My boyfriend.
- Whoa!
- Excuse me.
Sorry. This can't be happening.
Dae, I don't wanna talk to you.
Just leave me...
Sorry. I'm just looking for the loo.
I'm Alex Finnerty
from Melbourne, Australia.
I'm a new teacher here this year.
Why are you not Dae?
You mean the guy you don't wanna talk to?
Thank you.
- Did Kitty really leave?
- Yup.
Ugh, this is a nightmare.
Dae Heun Kim, get it together.
Even Mihee and Eunice asked me
about what was up with you and Kitty.
Tell your followers that
what I do is none of their business.
Well, now your business
is going to be my business too.
You know I told my mom
we've been dating since the summer, right?
You know you only told me that
four hours ago, right?
So can you stop looking for Kitty
and please start acting
like you're my boyfriend?
Everyone's watching.
Well, someone had a hot boy summer.
- Do you know where Juliana is?
- No. She hasn't texted back.
I'll call her.
The number you are
trying to reach is no longer in service.
The number you are trying to reach
is no longer in service.
Are you all right?
Can I get you anything?
- Never mind.
- You're American, right?
- Yes.
- I really admire you guys over there.
Why isn't Dae running after me?
- ...also very loud.
- What?
I noticed that Americans speak louder
than everyone else.
Forget everything that just happened.
I am going back in there
and I am not leaving without answers.
Excuse me.
This girl treats Korean guys like Pokémon.
She's trying to catch them all.
- Not interested.
- Get over yourself. I'm looking for Dae.
- Hey, can we stop now?
- No, we can't stop.
And here's why.
- Hello, Ms. Jeon!
- Yuri, hello.
Dae, we just got your tuition.
Things must have worked out.
What a relief!
Thank you.
You paid for the whole quarter?
Yep. I told you when we made our deal
that I'd figure it out.
I thought you meant
like a few hundred bucks.
Yeah, so now you really owe me.
Okay, who are you?
I'm Kitty Song Covey.
You're Kitty?
Wait, are you Q?
Track star, fellow American,
heart of gold?
Guilty as charged. I feel like
we should hug right now. Should we?
Maybe later. I need to find Dae.
So you're the pen pal?
If he's Q, then you must be Min Ho.
Of course you are.
Where's Dae?
All right, fine...
But why do you even need a fake boyfriend?
You think your mom will be glad to know
you were seduced by her chauffeur's son?
Ew.
You seduce me?
Mom will think
I'm doing this for attention
and tell me
to break up with you immediately.
Still, it'll be better
than if she knew the truth.
Fine. Let's talk with her now and get this
over with. I hate hurting Kitty.
You can make up with her tomorrow.
Tonight, you're mine.
It's a dream come true
for me. I'm a huge K-pop fan.
My karaoke song list
is exclusively in Korean.
Oh.
Oh, Yuri, this is Madison,
the Millers' daughter.
Your father's having dinner
with her parents to discuss business.
Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Oh!
- Mom, you know Dae.
- Of course I know Dae.
- One of our best students.
- And my boyfriend.
Hello.
You're dating your tutor?
You said he's one of our best students.
- That's why he's your tutor.
- Oh, juicy.
I hope you're not angry, Ms. Ho Lim.
Of course I'm not angry.
Like I said,
Dae is one of our best students.
Great.
So did you get in touch
with Juliana's parents?
Yes, everything's fine.
We'll talk about it later.
- But...
- Madison, I want to introduce you
to our Korean language teacher,
Professor Chae.
- She'll be so impressed with you.
- Then why isn't Juliana here?
- What the hell is going on?
- It's not what it looks like.
It looks like you're a cheater.
Are you not upset?
He's been cheating on both of us.
No, he's been cheating on you.
I knew about you already.
Dae's American pen pal.
I didn't know you were you this morning.
Yuri, can we get a photo?
Sorry, I'm late.
You're here now, darling.
Is Yuri dating our driver's son?
Is this...
lettuce?
So this is my answer.
I fell for a guy who was a total liar,
a total fake.
I can't believe I wasted years of my life
being in love with this person.
Whoa!
What? Never seen a girl
crash into a dessert tower before?
Nothing to see here, people!
Oh!
Fine, maybe there is something to see.
- Kitty, are you okay?
- Get away from me.
♪ I wish I left all my things
At your place ♪
♪ So I could come get them ♪
♪ And say that we could make exceptions ♪
♪ I just can't take the rejection... ♪
Thank you for calling
Asianair. For Korean, press one.
For English, press two.
A representative
will be ready to assist you momentarily.
Just breathe, Kitty.
You can go home.
You don't have to die here
from a broken heart.
Your current wait time
is 70 minutes. Please continue to hold.
Spill it!
When did you get with Yuri? And where?
- And how far?
- And most importantly, why?
Dae, you little scammer.
Dae?
How did you convince Yuri
to buy you that suit?
How do you know I didn't buy it?
Because it costs 5K.
- Seriously?
- I don't know. I feel bad for Kitty.
- I don't.
- That's cold, Min Ho.
Breaking up with someone is brutal.
Except it wasn't a breakup
because it wasn't a real relationship.
No one's gonna blame you for upgrading
a pen pal for an actual girlfriend.
Marius?
No, no, no.
I thought Marius went back to Greece.
- Maybe he changed his mind.
- Hmm.
Oy, Marius. Wake up! Time for class!
A little help.
Dae's crazy ex-pen pal
broke into our dorm to murder us.
This is my room.
- You're listed as Song Covey.
- So?
Song can be a guy's name. That's why
they assigned you to the guys' dorm.
What?
She did this on purpose.
To be closer to Dae and me.
- Okay.
- I told you lot,
she was hitting on me
on the plane ride over.
- I was not hitting on you.
- Kitty.
Can we please talk?
No, I never wanna speak to you again.
- Kitty.
- I want my necklace back.
Your necklace?
Yeah, the one I gave you
when your mom died.
Yeah, I have it around here somewhere.
Somewhere?
I'll find it.
You don't even know where it is.
Dae, that belonged to my mom.
I'll bring it back to you, Kitty.
I promise.
Your promises are literally worthless.
All of Dae's stuff is in
the room. Where's he going to sleep?
Here, man.
Great.
I know you're trying to be a hero by
letting that tourist crash here tonight,
but this isn't a hostel.
Hostels are filled with friendly people.
I'm friendly to my friends.
You somehow managed to land
the only daughter in one of the richest,
most well-connected families in the world.
Full stop.
Don't blow it.
You also have the love of your life
20 feet away from you.
Don't blow that.
Quit hogging the blanket.
Siri, play "Reykjavik New Year's Eve Mix."
The number you are
trying to reach is no longer in service.
♪ You can hold on, just hold on
Hold on to me, to me ♪
♪ Looking for a sign to say it's right
Well, then here's the green light ♪
♪ The green light
So come on over, baby ♪
♪ Dance the night away
While we're both young ♪
♪ Can't you see that you're ready
The feeling's heavy ♪
♪ I can barely breathe
I'm floating on your cloud to stay alive ♪
♪ I'm just trying to keep
This moment forever ♪
♪ Feel this moment we treasure ♪
♪ Dancing, dancing
Till the morning light ♪
♪ I just wanna see
You and me together ♪
♪ You and me together always... ♪
Thank you.
I'll be at the airport by 9 a.m.
for the standby seat.
Wait. Is that...?
I'm standing exactly where Mom stood.
Wait.
Is this a sign that I should stay?
Kitty, me and Yuri, it's not real.
It's all fake.
Will you just open the door?
I can explain.
Begging is not a good look.
I wasn't begging.
I was just trying to get my pants.
Listen, you squatter, we have to get
ready for the first day of school.
Don't make us late.
And she's gone.
Sweet.
Dae, don't worry about it. We'll...
President Han?
That guy is way too extreme.
It's 2022 for crying out loud,
he can't throw fits like that.
Every single person deserves respect.
No one deserves that kind of abuse.
Fortunately,
it's only on the Korean news, sir.
President Han?
It's actually also on the BBC right now-
- Huh?
- Not the BBC!
CEO Sung-jin Han
is the latest troubled dynasty
now facing calls
of atonement from political
and religious leaders in South Korea.
Business experts say his behavior
threatens Han Hotel Group's
acquisition of the ultra-conservative,
American-based Miller Hospitality.
The Miller family
famously grew their hotel empire
from small, humble beginnings in Iowa.
We've just received word
that Mr. Han's own daughter
has posted this meme
of her father's outburst.
Whoa, that was fast.
You ungrateful, spoiled little brat!
Are you trying to ruin me?
Do you realize
you are destroying our family?
This is why we should never
have raised her abroad.
She has no respect!
Calm down.
If there's any hope of closing this deal,
Mr. Han will have to do damage control...
Turn that off!
President Han,
what if we hire back that chef?
Whatever I do right now
will only look performative.
I have a solution.
Your one precious daughter
has been dating
your chauffeur's son all summer.
And you welcomed him with open arms.
- I did?
- Yes.
Invited him to your home.
And your workplace too.
When should we call the press conference?
- President Han, how about tomorrow?
- Do it immediately.
Yes, sir.
You go get dressed right now.
Kitty!
I've been all over campus
trying to find you.
Listen, what you saw yesterday, me...
Sorry.
Um...
The truth is that...
- Why is she calling me?
- 'Cause she's your girlfriend.
No. Just let me explain, Kitty.
No.
After everything, there's nothing
you can say that's gonna make me stay.
Maybe there's something I can do.
It's happening.
Dae Heun!
- Dad?
Finally. A word I know.
- Your dad is Yuri's driver? I thought...
- Sorry.
- What are you doing here?
- President Han is looking for you.
Why me?
That's what I was gonna ask you.
Let's get going.
- Wait, one moment, I need to talk...
- No, no, we have to get going.
No...
President Han, your daughter
seems to have paid Dae Heun's tuition.
It seems her feelings for him are sincere.
We'll take over the payments.
As part of his new internship.
- Internship?
- Yes, sir.
And here's the NDA for him to sign.
Why is he wearing pajamas outside?
- You.
- Yes?
Take off your suit.
My... My suit?
Hey, we've got to go
to the press conference.
What press conference?
You said I could make up
with Kitty tomorrow. Tomorrow's now today.
Our deal is over.
The situation has changed.
We have some important
family business now,
otherwise I'd offer you a ride.
But I'd be happy to call you a Kakao taxi.
Hard pass.
Well, bon voyage.
It is important for me
to own up to all my decisions...
Dae, have you seen this video?
It's kind of blowing up.
I bet Yuri's loving this drama.
I don't particularly care.
Kitty.
- I thought you left.
- I did, but then I decided to stay.
And not that it's any of your business,
but this isn't all about a boy.
Oh, sweetie.
My mom went here, and...
I don't know, being here just makes me
feel closer to her than I ever have.
And...
Wait, Dae's on TV?
...but for my wife, and my daughter.
Family means everything to me.
And so, I'd like to apologize
for my behavior.
Dae looks miserable.
Something about this isn't right.
Today, I'm announcing
the Han Hotel Youth Internship Program.
The first intern is Dae Heun Kim.
Son of my longtime driver.
A top student
at Korean Independent School of Seoul.
And he also happens to be
dating my daughter, Yuri.
Any questions? Yes.
Thank you. Actually,
this question is for Dae Heun Kim.
I'm just curious. Do you believe
Mr. Han is being sincere
and not using you to repair his image?
Yeah. Um...
I believe Mr. Han means what he said.
Um...
He will do better.
So...
"lettuce" move on.
Thank you.
Well played.
Oh, my God.
He's faking it.
That's a fake relationship.